(Howard:)What is happening?
(Howard:)Are we missing him?
(Bernadette:)No, that's not what
this feeling is.
(Bernadette:)Is it?
(Howard:)Of course not.
He drove us crazy.
(Howard:)Like when you were gonna
make that pie
(Howard:)and Stuart ate
all the blueberries. (scoffs)
(Bernadette:)And he tried to deny it, but
his teeth were all purple.
(Howard:)That was pretty cute.
(chuckles)
(Penny:)Yeah.
Ew, we are missing him!
(Raj:)So I was thinking,
maybe we can come up with a name
(Raj:)for the asteroid by
combining our names.
(Sheldon:)That's a great idea.
(Sheldon:)I've got it.
(Sheldon:)We'll call it... Cooper.
(Raj:)How is that both our names?
"Koo" from Koothrappali
and "per" from Cooper.
(Raj:)Yeah, s-so it's, like,
Kooper with a "K"?
(Sheldon:)Nah, you're right, that's dumb.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Leonard, great news.
(Sheldon:)We discovered a medium-sized
asteroid together.